<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pracula&#39;s Corner</title>
    <link>https://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pracula&#39;s Corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 20:00:20 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let me teach you how to set up Hugo!</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/set_up_hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 20:00:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/set_up_hugo/</guid>
      <description>What is Hugo? Hugo is simply a static site generator. What it does is that it allows you to build static websites by just editing your Markdown files and it will create the HTML code. It also does this blazingly fast, so it lets you compile hundreds of thousands of pages with very minimal downtime.&#xA;Why would I want to learn this? Good question! I was also wondering why anyone would want to learn about Hugo, as there are plenty of good platforms where we can write and it would be appreciated just as well, and might even get a better reach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Its an interesting time to start blogging</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:12:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I had no clue it was this easy to get started on blogging. Untill now, I had thought it would be a pain to configure a website just for blogs, as that would take a lot of resources and time that I would probably not have 2 days before a semester exam.&#xA;The config of a theme, the HTML and CSS styling, understanding how to configure the posts in a clear way in my database, all seemed too challenging.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
